https://www.scotusblog.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
This privacy policy governs the manner in which SCOTUSblog collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from readers (each, a “Reader”) of the https://www.scotusblog.com website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by SCOTUSblog.
Personal identification information
We may collect personal identification information from Readers in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Readers visit our site, subscribe to emails we send through MailChimp and Feedburner, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Readers may be asked for, as appropriate, name and email address. We will collect personal identification information from Readers only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Readers can always refuse to supply personal identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site-related activities.
Nonpersonal identification information
We may collect nonpersonal identification information about Readers whenever they interact with our Site. Nonpersonal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Readers’ means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the internet service providers utilized, and other similar information.
Web browser cookies
Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance Reader experience. A Reader’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. Readers may choose to set their web browsers to refuse cookies, or to alert them when cookies are being sent. If they do so, some parts of the Site may not function properly.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor had visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
How we use collected information
SCOTUSblog collects and uses Readers’ personal information for the following purposes:
– To personalize Reader experience
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Readers as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
– To improve our Site
We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from Readers.
How we protect your information
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.
What rights you have over your data
If you formerly left comments (which we’ve discontinued), you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal or security purposes.
Sharing your personal information
We do not sell, trade or rent Readers’ personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding Readers with our partners for the purposes outlined above. We may use third-party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
Third-party websites
Readers may find content on our Site that links to the sites and services of our partners, contributors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer-service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites that have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.
Changes to this privacy policy
SCOTUSblog has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Readers to check this page frequently for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
Your acceptance of these terms
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
Contacting us
If you have any questions about this privacy policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:
SCOTUSblog
https://www.scotusblog.com
7475 Wisconsin Avenue, Suite 850, Bethesda, MD 20814
###-###-####
feedback [at] scotusblog [dot] com
This document was last updated on May 25, 2018.
Privacy policy created by Generate Privacy Policy, with adjustments by the editors.
Featured Posts
Justices refuse to delay execution of Brandon Bernard
– Kalvis Golde
Argument analysis: Justices at odds over federal robocall ban in the face of technological change
– Amanda Shanor
States tell justices to deny Texas request to overturn 2020 election
– Amy Howe
Sponsored by Casetext
Enter the full sentence you want to support with case law
Search
SCOTUStalk see all
Email Digest Sign-UpReceive a daily email digest from Feedburner by entering your email.
Merits Case Pages and Archives
This term's merits cases
AMG Capital Management, LLC v. Federal Trade CommissionArizona Republican Party v. Democratic National CommitteeArkansas v. GreshamArthrex Inc. v. Smith & Nephew Inc.Azar v. GreshamBarr v. Alcaraz-EnriquezBarr v. DaiBorden v. United StatesBP P.L.C. v. Mayor and City Council of BaltimoreBrnovich v. Democratic National CommitteeBrownback v. KingCalifornia v. TexasCaniglia v. StromCargill, Inc. v. Doe ICarney v. AdamsCarr v. SaulCedar Point Nursery v. HassidCIC Services, LLC v. Internal Revenue ServiceCity of Chicago, Illinois v. FultonCollins v. MnuchinDavis v. SaulDepartment of Justice v. House Committee on the JudiciaryEdwards v. VannoyFacebook Inc. v. DuguidFederal Communications Commission v. Prometheus Radio ProjectFederal Republic of Germany v. PhilippFord Motor Company v. BandemerFord Motor Company v. Montana Eighth Judicial District CourtFulton v. City of Philadelphia, PennsylvaniaGoogle LLC v. Oracle America Inc.Henry Schein Inc. v. Archer and White Sales Inc.Jones v. MississippiLange v. CaliforniaMckesson v. DoeMnuchin v. CollinsNational Association of Broadcasters v. Prometheus Radio ProjectNestlé USA, Inc. v. Doe INiz-Chavez v. BarrPereida v. BarrPham v. Guzman ChavezRepublic of Hungary v. SimonRoman Catholic Diocese of Brooklyn, New York v. CuomoRutledge v. Pharmaceutical Care Management AssociationSalinas v. United States Railroad Retirement BoardSmith & Nephew Inc. v. Arthrex Inc.Tanzin v. TanvirTaylor v. RiojasTexas v. CaliforniaTexas v. New MexicoTorres v. MadridTrump v. New YorkTrump v. Sierra ClubU.S. Fish and Wildlife Service v. Sierra ClubUnited States v. Arthrex Inc.United States v. BriggsUnited States v. CollinsUnited States v. CooleyUzuegbunam v. PreczewskiVan Buren v. United StatesWolf v. Innovation Law Lab
Archives
Month
Dec 2020
Nov 2020
Oct 2020
Sept 2020
Aug 2020
July 2020
Term Snapshot
This Week at the CourtOn Monday, the court released additional orders from the Dec. 4 conference, in which the justices did not grant any new cases and called for the views of the federal government in one case. The justices also heard oral argument in Hungary v. Simon and Germany v. Philipp.On Tuesday, the justices heard oral argument in Facebook v. Duguid and Henry Schein v. Archer & White Sales.On Wednesday, the justices heard oral argument in Collins v. Mnuchin.On Thursday, the court released opinions in Tanzin v. Tanvir, Carney v. Adams, United States v. Briggs and Rutledge v. Pharmaceutical Care Management Association.On Friday, the justices will hold their Dec. 11 conference.
Statistical Snapshot
Cases granted for this term
45
Cases argued
28
Cases decided
4
Summary reversals
3
Cases granted for next term
0
see all »
At a Glance
Twitter Feed
Tweets by @SCOTUSblog
Calendar: December 2020
Full Calendar
Submit Event
Dec. 2020
SuMoTuWeThFrSa
1Nestlé USA v. Doe I (19-416)CIC Services v. IRS (19-930)
2Edwards v. Vannoy (19-5807)
3
4Conference
5
6
7OrdersHungary v. Simon (18-1447)Germany v. Philipp (19-351)
8Facebook v. Duguid (19-511)Henry Schein v. Archer & White (19-963)
9Collins v. Mnuchin (19-422)
10Opinions
11Conference
12
13
14Orders
15
16
17
Alito speaks at Federalist Society National Convention
On Thursday, Nov. 12, 2020, Justice Samuel Alito delivered the virtual keynote address at the annual Federalist Society National Convention.
Awards
Peabody AwardAwarded the Peabody Award for excellence in electronic media.
Sigma Delta ChiAwarded the Sigma Delta Chi deadline reporting award for online coverage of the Affordable Care Act decision.
National Press Club AwardAwarded the National Press Club's Breaking News Award for coverage of the Affordable Care Act decision.
Silver Gavel AwardAwarded the Silver Gavel Award by the American Bar Association for fostering the American public’s understanding of the law and the legal system.
American Gavel AwardAwarded the American Gavel Award for Distinguished Reporting About the Judiciary to recognize the highest standards of reporting about courts and the justice system.
Webby AwardAwarded the Webby Award for excellence on the internet.
Switch to desktop siteor Download our Apple or Android App
Switch to mobile site
This website may use cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can leave if you wish.Accept Read MorePrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Necessary
Necessary
Always Enabled
